Wiphaphorn Phoemphoklang

Software Developer

■ wiphaphorn.wp@gmail.com

098-8615496

My portfolio

■ Github

After graduated from the Junior Software Developer program (Bootcamp) at Generation Thailand. Continuously improved my coding skills through personal projects and online courses to stay competitive in the job market. My diverse work experience has enabled me to adapt to changing situations and collaborate effectively in teams. With my passion for continuous self-improvement, I am dedicated to becoming a Software Developer with expertise in the future.

Experience

SAP PROGRAMMER (ABAPER) | ASIA METAL PUBLIC COMPANY LIMITED

APR 2024 - July 2024

- · Receive requirements, analyze, and design work processes in the SAP system.
- Develop programs, reports, and user exits according to new requirements and enhance existing systems to operate more efficiently.
- · Prepare documentation for system changes and support users when they encounter problems using the SAP system.
- JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER | GENERATION THAILAND (BOOTCAMP) NOV 2023 - FEB 2024
 - Learned about building web applications and have a project assignment that requires applying all the knowledge acquired, incorporating both front-end and back-end skills.
 - · Learned how to apply behavior skills and a growth mindset when encountering real-world situations and methods for adjusting them appropriately to fit the specific circumstances.

OPERATIONS OFFICER | KIATNAKIN PHATRA BANK

AUG 2018 - MAY 2022

- · Maintain accurate and up-to-date records of transactions, customer interactions, and compliance-related documentation.
- · Prepare reports for management review, regulatory reporting, and audits and collaborate with other departments to achieve common goals.
- · Provide support and training to junior staff members as needed and stay informed about regulatory changes and updates affecting banking operations.

Education

High School | Wisutthikasatree School French-English Language

2012 - 2015

Skills

- HTML5
- CSS
- · Tailwind CSS
- JavaScript
- · React.js

- Node.js
- · Express.js
- MongoDB
- ABAP(Advanced Business Application Personal Responsibility Programming)
- Problem-solving
- · Growth mindset
- Adaptability
- Communication

 - Teamwork

CERTIFICATION

- Junior Software Developer Program (Cohort 6) GENERATION THAILAND | Feb 2024
- Learn SQL Course Codecademy | Feb 2024
- Learn React Course Codecademy | Feb 2024
- Learn JavaScript Course Codecademy | Dec 2023
- Learn CSS Course Codecademy | Dec 2023
- Learn HTML Course Codecademy | Nov 2023